<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".Terms_and_Conditions">


    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/topgreen"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="@drawable/toptermsandconditions"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        />

    <ImageView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentTop="true"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
        android:layout_marginLeft="20dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="371dp"
        android:background="@drawable/backbtn3" />



    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/terms_and_conditionsTXT"
        android:layout_width="300dp"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
        android:layout_marginTop="70dp"
        android:text="@string/terms_and_conditions"
        android:textSize="25sp"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:gravity="center"
        style="@style/TextAppearance.Material3.BodyLarge"
        />


    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/termsScroll"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="400dp"
        android:layout_centerInParent="true">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/lorem"
            android:layout_width="380dp"
            android:layout_height="450dp"
            android:layout_below="@+id/topgreen"
            android:layout_centerHorizontal="true"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:paddingLeft="20dp"
            android:paddingRight="40dp"
            android:scrollbars="vertical"
            android:text="     By accessing and using the Poultry Management App, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions. The App is provided on an as is and as available basis, and we do not guarantee its accuracy, completeness, or reliability. You acknowledge that the use of the App is at your own risk and discretion. The App is intended for informational and management purposes only and should not be considered as professional advice. We are not liable for any damages or losses arising from your use of the App. You agree not to use the App for any unlawful or prohibited purpose, and you are solely responsible for your interactions with other users of the App. We reserve the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue the App at any time without prior notice. Your continued use of the App after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised terms and conditions. We may collect and use your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using the App, you consent to such collection and use of your data. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the developers, owners, and affiliates of the App from any claims, damages, or liabilities arising from your use of the App or violation of these terms and conditions. These terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and us regarding the use of the App, superseding any prior agreements. These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of, and any disputes arising hereunder shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts."
            android:textSize="19sp"

            />
    </ScrollView>

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/acceptBTN"
        android:layout_width="160dp"
        android:layout_height="50dp"
        android:text="ACCEPT"
        android:layout_marginTop="50dp"
        android:layout_below="@+id/termsScroll"
        android:layout_marginLeft="40dp"
        android:backgroundTint="#0df99f"
        />

    <Button
        android:id="@+id/declineBTN"
        android:layout_width="160dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="DECLINE"
        android:textColor="@color/black"
        android:backgroundTint="#d9d9d9"
        android:layout_marginTop="50dp"
        android:layout_below="@+id/termsScroll"
        android:layout_toRightOf="@+id/acceptBTN"
        android:layout_marginLeft="20dp"
        />



</RelativeLayout>